https://theatreconsultants.org/privacy

Home Privacy
Effective April 20, 2006
The American Society of Theatre Consultants (ASTC) is committed to protecting any personal information that you may provide to us. In particular, we believe it is important for you to know how we treat information about you that we may receive from this Web site.
Information Collected
Use of Collected Information
Links to Other Sites
Security of Collected Information
Access to Collected Information
Contacting Us
Changes to this Policy
Information Collected
In general, you can visit this Web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. Our web servers also seek (as many Web sites do) to place a "cookie" (a small data file) on your computer’s hard drive which allows the server to determine the computer when it visits again, in order to track statistical information about navigation to and throughout certain areas of our site, and to ASTC promotions on other sites. This cookie is not used to obtain your name or any personal data, and the information that is tracked is used only for internal purposes.
In addition, there are portions of this Web site where we may need to collect personal information from you for a specific purpose, such as to provide you with certain information you request. The information collected from you may include your name, address, telephone, fax number, or e-mail address.
This Web site is not intended for persons under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children..
Return to top
Use of Collected Information
Domain name information that we collect is not used to personally identify you and instead is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site.
When other information is collected from you, such as your name and e-mail address, we generally let you know at the time of collection how we will use the personal information. Usually, we use the personal information you provide only to respond to your inquiry or to process your request. This information may be shared with other ASTC businesses, but only if necessary to fulfill your request or for related purposes.
We may share the personal information you provide with other companies we have hired to provide services for us. These companies – our vendors – are contractually bound to use personal information we share with them only to perform the services we have hired them to provide. We do not share, sell, or lease personal information about you to any third-parties for their marketing use. We will release information about you if you direct us to do so, if we are required by law to do so, or in other legally limited circumstances.
If you register with one of ASTC’s business units online, they may use this information to provide you with custom information about ASTC’s offerings in support of your business needs. You should review the privacy policy associated with that ASTC business’ Web site for further information about that ASTC business’ privacy practices.
Return to top
Links to Other Sites
ASTC’s Web site may contain links to other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the content, security, or privacy practices employed by other sites.
Security of Collected Information
We maintain strict physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect your personal information from unauthorized or inappropriate access. We restrict access to information about you to those ASTC workers who need to know the information to respond to your inquiry or request. Workers who misuse personal information are subject to disciplinary action.
Access to Collected Information
You may review and update the information that you provide to us through this Web site by contacting us as described below.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please use the Contact Us page. We welcome your questions and suggestions about our privacy policy.
Changes to this Policy
Please check this privacy policy periodically to inform yourself of any changes. Although we reserve the right to modify or supplement this privacy policy, we will provide notice to you on this Web site of any major changes for at least 30 days following the change.
Duane Wilson, Secretary/CFOAmerican Society of Theatre ConsultantsPO Box 22La Luz, NM 88337855-800-2782
Return to top
